-女浩克  -女浩克
She-Hulk? She-Hulk. She-Hulk.
浩克女士 浩克女孩 女浩克... 他们高兴就好
Lady-Hulk, Girl-Hulk, She-Hulk. Give 'em what they want.
前情提要
Previously on She-Hulk...
希望人们赶紧忘了这名字
That name better not stick.
要是你的资料用女浩克呢
What if you made a profile as She-Hulk?
匹配 女浩克
我知道这么做不好
I'm not proud of this.
还有比30多岁相亲更糟心的事吗
Is there anything worse than dating in your 30s?
其实我是你的粉丝
I have to admit, I was a fan.
你在法庭上大战泰坦妮亚
I mean, your battle with Titania in court,
简直是太不可思议了
- it was incredible.
“释放泰坦妮亚”运动的支持者 于今日举行庆祝活动
Supporters of the Free Titania movement are celebrating
-针对她的全部指控均已被撤销 -哦
- that she's been cleared of all charges. - Boo.
我这里有一份法庭文件 是泰坦妮亚环球有限公司递交的
I've got court documents filed by Titania Worldwide LLC.
原告 泰坦妮亚女浩克系列 被告 珍妮佛
She's suing me over the name "She-Hulk"?
她因为我用了“女浩克”的名字告我
这是我的名字啊
But that's my name.
泰坦妮亚女浩克系列
力量是美丽的呈现 美丽是力量的表达
Strength is beauty. Beauty is strength.
谁令你光彩夺目
What makes you beautiful?
泰坦妮亚“女浩克”系列
She-Hulk by Titania.
展示力量 展现美丽 只做你自己
Be strong, be beautiful. Own who you are.
泰坦妮亚“女浩克”系列
She-Hulk by Titania.
我是力量的化身 我是美丽的代言
I am strength. I am beauty.
我只做我自己
I own who I am.
泰坦妮亚“女浩克”系列
She-Hulk by Titania,
全新奢华护肤彩妆健康产品
a luxurious new line of skin care, beauty, and wellness products
泰坦妮亚为你量身定做
created by Titania exclusively for you.
泰坦妮亚女浩克系列
She-Hulk by Titania.
你正在收听的是 专家普法面面谈节目
You're listening to Pro Say, Law 360's podcast.
我们的赞助商要和各位打个招呼
A quick word from our sponsor.
嘿 粉丝们 我已经等不及和你们见面了
Hey, Titaniacs, can't wait to see you all.
-切德 -你好啊 珍妮佛
- Ched! - Yo. What's up, Jen?
你怎么不打招呼就直接来了
You can't just walk into my house!
我还要怎么打招呼  刚才不是打过了嘛
What do you want me to tell you? I just did.
这些签名版的“女浩克”商品 准能大赚一笔
I'm making a killing selling these signed She-Hulk products.
大家都爱你 大家都爱女浩克
They love you. The people love the She-Hulk.
-所以快来给我签名吧 -我不签
- So I need your John Hancock for me. - I'm not signing those.
什么叫你不签  我这可是在给你的生意捧场
What do you mean? I'm supporting your business venture.
这些东西不是我的 和我毫无关系
No, this is not mine. It has nothing to do with me.
-可是标签上有你的名字啊 -那是别人干的
- It's got your name here on the label. - This is someone else.
那个女的 泰坦妮亚 用了我的名字注册商标
This woman, Titania, has trademarked my name.
你太蠢了 为什么让她这么干
That's dumb. Why would you let her do that?
不是我让她干的 切德
I didn't let her, Ched.
珍妮佛 你要知道
You know, Jen,
商标这个东西就是
the way trademark works is,
谁先注册的就归谁
whoever gets there first, gets it.
当初要是你先注册了 那她就没机会了
So if you would've done yours first, she wouldn't have been able to do that.
泰坦妮亚“女浩克”系列
谢谢
Thank you.
她发了条推特 说会在这里和粉丝互动
She tweeted that she'd be here connecting with her fans.
你还关注她了
You follow her?
为了侦查敌情呀 你要去哪
It's for reconnaissance. Where are you going?
-我要跟她摊牌去 -好 必须去
- To talk to her. - Yeah, we are.
去摊牌还排什么队 开玩笑吧
But we're not waiting in line. You kidding?
直接大大方方地进去 这样才对 请让一下
We enter with confidence. That's how it works. Excuse us.
这都是什么
What is this?
“蛇毒精华丰唇霜”
"Snake venom lip plumper."
她真的在卖蛇油
She's literally selling snake oil.
“美肤精华”
"Beauty serum."
“美肤精油”
"Beauty oil."
“美肤凝露” 这些不是一样的吗
"Beauty tonic." How are these not all exactly the same thing?
开什么玩笑 当然不一样
Are you kidding? They're completely different.
试用装
Free samples?
给Z 爱你 泰坦妮亚
这些都是给我们的啊
These are all for me and that girl.
太感谢你了
- Thank you so much, thank you.
不好意思 小朋友 去那边排队
I'm so sorry, little child, but the line starts way back there.
我不是来插队的
I don't wanna cut.
我要求你停止卖这些东西
I want you to stop, and take all of this down.
有什么问题吗
What's the issue?
你盗用我的名字卖这些垃圾产品 居然还要告我
You're using my name to sell your trashy products, and you're suing me?
接受现实吧 珍妮佛 女浩克这个名字是我的
Get over it, Jennifer. The name She-Hulk is mine.
不好意思
Excuse me?
能帮我们合个影吗
Could you take a photo?
天啊 当然可以 后退一点 给我点地方
Oh, my God, yes. Back up a little bit. Just give me some space.
-她要... -你要给她们拍
- She's gonna... - You taking it?
就拍一张 下不为例
Just one, and that is it.
她就这么明目张胆地盗用我名字 太不要脸了
I can't believe she stole my name.
反正你也不喜欢女浩克这个名字
But you said you didn't like that name anyways.
-我是不喜欢 -行吧
- I don't. - Okay.
大家都这么叫我 仅此而已 并不是真正的我
It's just what people decided to call me. It's not who I am.
我仍然是珍妮佛·沃尔特斯
I'm still Jennifer Walters.
成为女浩克只是机缘巧合而已
She-Hulk is just a thing that happened to me.
-你能这么想也挺好的 -不过我得承认 女浩克也有好处
- That's a really good perspective to have. - I admit there are parts that I enjoy.
-好吧 你这是话里有话啊 -比如迷人的长发 不会喝醉
- Okay, you're not done. - Like the amazing hair, no hangover.
走夜路回家时戴着耳机也不害怕
Walking home with headphones on without being afraid.
-这可是每个女人的梦想 -但是我就是我
- Every woman's dream. - But I'm not a different person
我也不需要另一个名字
who needs a different name.
好吧 所以你对女浩克这名字 没那么不爽了
Okay. So you're not mad at the name She-Hulk?
当然 我无所谓
No, I don't care about it.
-好吧 那这事就翻篇了  -对 我已经差不多翻篇了
- Okay. So you're totally over it? - Yeah, like, the most over it.
你把订书器捏碎了
You're crushing your stapler.
你说什么
What?
为什么她的东西卖得这么贵啊
Why does she have to charge her fans so much for everything?
这就是套路呀 妮基 所以她是有钱人 你却穷得叮当响
Because that's smart, Nikki. That's why she is rich and you're broke.
忙什么呢 妮基
What's happening, Nik?
忙着自言自语呢
Oh, I was just talking to myself.
我不是来找你闲聊的 你得帮我个忙
I can't pretend I'm here for a friendly visit. I need a favor.
我帮忙可贵了
Oh. well, you know my price.
-人情得还 利息单算 -没问题
- Return favor. Plus interest. - Done.
-说吧 -你能跟我一起排队
- Okay. - Stand in line with me
抢一下限量版球鞋吗
waiting for a sneaker drop?
“钢铁侠三代”要发售了 而且每人只能买一双
The Iron Man Threes are coming out. They're limited to one pair per customer.
你为什么需要两双呢
Why do you need two pairs?
一双穿 一双收藏
One to rock and one to stock.
好吧 你的意思是你花钱买鞋
Okay, so you're telling me that you collect shoes
只供起来看 完全不会穿
to look at that you're never gonna wear?
佩服
I respect that.
不是我显摆
I'm not gonna brag to you or anything,
但是我确实收了几双稀有限量版
but I do have some pretty rare limited editions
我的潮牌买手专供的
that I got from my drip broker.
专供...得了吧 什么潮牌买手
Through your... Excuse me, your what?
是的 我认识一哥们 叫阿朗佐 专做潮牌
Yeah, I got a guy, Alonzo, the drip broker.
这些时尚的玩意 你要什么他都搞得到
He can find anything you're looking for, fashion-wise.
这个潮牌买手能找到 定制服装的人吗
Can this drip broker find someone who could do custom clothing
要适合超能人类体型的
for, say, a super-human sized person?
绝对没问题
No doubt.
好吧 你现在就把人情还回来吧
Okay. I'm gonna need to call in my favor right now.
-你答应帮我的事还没干呢 -我不收你利息了
- You haven't done my favor. - I'm letting you slide on the interest.
可以
You're right.
好吧 真有你的 妮基
- You're right. Slick Nik. Slick Nik.
我要感谢所有亲爱的粉丝们
I just wanted to thank all of my beloved Titaniacs
-帮我实现了... -我已经翻篇了 真的
- for helping me reach my... - I'm over it. I really am.
这不是珍珠奶茶店吗
This is a boba café.
阿朗佐说这只是个幌子 实际做的是超级英雄服装生意
Alonzo says that it's a front for a superhero clothing business.
好吧
Okay.
-你好 想喝点什么  -你好啊 朋友
- Hi, are you ready to order? - Hey, how you doing, man?
我哥们阿朗佐让我来的
My boy Alonzo sent me.
阿朗佐 好的 你想喝什么
Alonzo. Okay, what's the order?
不 是我哥们 阿朗佐
No, no. My boy, Alonzo,
潮牌买手
the drip broker.
他介绍我来的
He sent me.
和超级英雄有关的
For the superhero stuff.
这里是奶茶店
This is a boba café.
我们不是警察
What is that, Chinese? I'm not Chinese.
你说的是中文吗 我不是中国人
我说我们不是警察
Well, I said we're not cops.
我说的是中文
And I said it in Chinese.
我觉得很丢脸
I feel so much shame.
-他生气了 我冒犯到他了 我... -没事的
- He's mad. I offended him. I... - Okay.
到后面来
Come to the back.
-好 -到了惊悚密室的桥段了
- All right. - Creepy back-room situation.
-感觉有点假 -好吧
- This kind of hustle. - Okay.
你要买什么 我这货很全
What do you need? I got everything.
美国队长的盾牌 雷神的锤子
Captain America shield, Thor hammer.
复仇者联盟的T恤
Avengers T-shirt.
这上面印的是“复犰者”
This says, "Avongers."
你要是不喜欢这件 我还有“腹仇者”
You don't like Avongers? I got Avingers.
也是印错的
Oh, with an I.
我还挺喜欢的
I kind of like this.
好吧 我们不要这种山寨货 懂吗
Okay, no, we don't want bootleg stuff, okay?
我们要的是给超级英雄的定制款
I want custom-made clothing for a superhero.
听着 如果你不是我们要找的人 那你认识我们要找的人吗
Question, if you're not the guy, then do you know who the guy is?
他才不会见你们呢 他可是超级大咖
He won't meet you. He's exclusive.
好吧 看来认识那个人
Okay. So you do know the guy.
好吧 我买那件复犰者 这样行了吧
Okay, fine. I'll buy one of your Avongers T-shirts.
-外加配套的帽子 -行 要买就买一整套
- And a matching hat. - Yes, I wanna complete the ensemble.
好的
Okay.
别碰
No.
你好
Hi.
我要和你谈谈 我有个客户想买你的定制衣服...
I wanted to talk to you about making clothing for my client...
谁介绍你来的
Do you have a referral?
泰坦妮亚介绍我来的
Titania referred me.
我看见你耸肩了 不见
I saw you shrug. Rejected.
其实我的客户是一位复仇者
Actually, my client is an Avenger.
-而且是主力之一 先生 -没错
- She's one of the top-tier ones, sir. - Yes.
给你们十五分钟 我的助理会安排时间
Fifteen-minute consultation. My assistant will set up the appointment.
我还能看见你们呢
I can still see you.
-好吧 -好的 先生 谢谢您
- Okay. Okay. - Yes, sir. Thank you.
您找我有事吗
Is everything all right, sir?
对
No.
为什么我今天在圣莫妮卡大道
Why did I pass a billboard on Santa Monica Boulevard today
看见广告牌上是 女浩克牌翘臀霜的广告
advertising a She-Hulk booty boost smoothie?
那个和我没关系
Oh, so, that's not actually me.
严格意义上说 女浩克这个名字也不属于我
So that name was never really mine, officially.
是那些媒体的人先这么称呼我的
Everyone in the media just started calling me that.
但是现在这个无比讨厌 有点小超能力的女人...
But now this incredibly awful, slightly super-powered woman...
不用说了 因为这些我都不关心
Uh, yeah, I'm gonna stop you, 'cause none of that's my concern.
好吧
Okay.
古利库霍律所雇用女浩克
GLK and H made She-Hulk the face
做超能人类法务部的负责人
of our superhuman law division.
而我们现在却卷入了 一场无谓的法律诉讼
And now, we find ourselves in the middle of a frivolous lawsuit.
谁会去找一个官司缠身的律所呢
No one hires a firm that can't handle its own messes.
我会搞定这件事的 老板
I am going to fix this, sir.
不 用不着你
No, you won't.
虽然有点意外 但是也松了口气 你还没有傻到
I'm surprised and relieved you aren't foolish enough
想要为自己辩护
to try to represent yourself.
至少你还懂基本的规矩
At least you know that basic rule.
我接这个案子是出于职业操守
I'm taking this on as a professional courtesy,
但是接下来 我们就不是同事了
but moving forward, we are not colleagues.
我是你的律师 你是我的委托人 这是唯一可行的方式
I'm the attorney, you're the client. That's the only way this can work.
接受吗
Agreed?
接受
Agreed.
你为什么自己没注册商标
Why didn't you trademark your pseudonym?
我完全没想过这件事 谁能想得到呢
I never even thought about it, you know? Why would I?
奇异博士注册他的名字了吗  雷神也没有吧
Did Doctor Strange have to trademark his name? Did Thor?
你说的这两个人 用的就是他们的真名
You chose two examples of people who use their real names.
这就是让你在法律上 无计可施的人吗
This is the person who legally outmaneuvered you?
对
Yeah.
我们要表现得强硬一点 我们要提出反诉
We need to show strength. Countersue.
明确你在商标注册日期之前
Establish you were using the name
就开始以职业身份 使用女浩克这个名字了
in a professional capacity before the trademark date,
而泰坦妮亚的获利是基于
and Titania is profiting off name recognition
大众对这个名字的既有认知
already established in the marketplace.
如果你想成为我的客户 你的着装必须庄重得体
If you're gonna be my client, dress like you respect yourself,
不能穿得像个去法庭认罪的 醉驾橄榄球运动员
and not like a football player pleading no contest to a DUI.
妮基
Nikki?
怎么了 我没偷听 我正好在旁边
Yes? Wasn't lurking. I was close by.
显然你花了大把时间在穿着打扮上
You obviously spend a lot of time thinking about what you wear.
-要不帮帮她  -这件事我已经在办了
- Why don't you help her? - I'm actually already on top of that.
我帮你约了一个大咖 他专门为超级英雄做衣服
I got you a consultation with the guy who makes clothing for superheroes.
-我觉得没必要吧 -有必要
- Oh, I don't think I really need that. - You do, yeah.
西装不错 史瑞克
Nice suit, Shrek.
全体起立 现在正式开庭
All rise. Court is now in session.
厄尔利法官
法官大人 我恳请您批准 撤销这场无谓的恶意诉讼
Your Honor, we move to dismiss this entirely frivolous suit.
我的委托人 是“女浩克”商标的注册人
My client owns the trademark for She-Hulk.
或许布克小姐喜欢浪费司法资源
Ms. Book may enjoy wasting the court's time,
但是我们绝对不会这么做
but you can be certain that I do not.
布克小姐 你呢
Ms. Book?
谢谢您 法官大人
Thank you, Your Honor.
本案的主要事实不存在真正的争议
As you will see, there are no issues of fact here
无需开庭审理
that would require proceeding to trial.
由于珍妮佛·沃尔特斯的首次亮相 就是浩克的形象
Since the first public appearance of Jennifer Walters in her Hulk form,
大众已经普遍将她和女浩克的名字 联系在了一起
the public has unanimously identified her with the name She-Hulk.
事实上 没有任何公开证据表明
In fact, the name had not even been recorded
女浩克这个名字 在她登场之前就已经存在
in public discourse until that debut.
我们收集了 相关的新闻报道与广播摘要
We have a number of news items and broadcast quotes
作为证据提交给法庭
I'd like to enter into record.
简单来讲
Simply put,
被告是在利用我的委托人
the defendant is exploiting goodwill towards my client
和她知名度更高的表哥的商誉
and her better-known cousin,
售卖未经美国食药监管局批准的 伪劣产品
in order to sell her non-FDA approved sham products.
因此我申请法庭
We ask the court to grant our motion
对本案做出即决判决 并支持我方对赔偿的相关主张
for summary judgment, and order our requested remedies.
好吧
Okay.
首先 你说“伪劣”
First of all, "sham"?
你怎么不去看看 网上无数粉丝的反馈
Why don't you try telling that to the thousands of testimonials
大家用了我独家推出的 女浩克系列足部去角质膏后
from my fans who have had nothing but amazing results
都赞叹效果惊人
with my exclusive line of She-Hulk Foot Exfoliants,
我正好带了这个产品的试用装
which I just so happen to have a little sample of,
作为证据提交 谢谢
and offer into evidence, thank you.
不 我们不需要...
No, we don't need...
可以不要跑题吗
Can we please stay on track here?
法官大人 我的委托人 想要表达的是 女浩克不是...
What my client is trying to say is that She-Hulk was not...
你可以坐下了
You can sit down.
我的委托人想要表达的是 在以女浩克命名的产品线推出
What my client is trying to say is that Ms. Walters was not interested
并大获成功之前
in the She-Hulk name until it became associated
珍妮佛·沃尔特斯根本不在意 女浩克这个名字
with this incredibly successful line of products.
请播放一下
If we may.
-女浩克 -我不会回应那个名字的
- She-Hulk! Hey, She-Hulk! - I will not answer to that name.
知道为什么吗  因为那根本就不是我的名字
You know why? 'Cause it's not my name.
女浩克
She-Hulk! She-Hulk!
我的名字从来不是 以后也不会是女浩克
My name never has been, and never will be She-Hulk.
既没创意 也没气势 简直就是个垃圾名字
It's lazy, it's reductive, and it's straight-up garbage.
原告需要回应吗 布克小姐
Any response, Ms. Book?
当然需要 我们也想播放一条视频
Actually, yes. We have one more clip to show.
给我们讲讲 你是怎么想到女浩克这个名字的
Tell us, how did you come up with the name She-Hulk?
不知道是哪个新闻记者 起的这个名字
Some random guy on the news came up with it.
然后就传开了 所以现在 不管我喜不喜欢
But it stuck, and so now, whether I like it or not,
我就永远变成女浩克了
I am forever She-Hulk.
我的委托人很清楚地表明 她的名字叫女浩克
My client clearly stated that she is She-Hulk.
这只是一个个例
This is just one instance.
你是否能证明沃尔特斯小姐 平时也在频繁使用这个名字
Can you prove a pattern of Ms. Walter's personal use of the name?
可以 法官大人 这方面我们的证据很充分
Yes, Your Honor, we definitely have more to present.
希望如此
You'd better.
否则我会更倾向于被告一方
Or I'm inclined to side with the defendant.
周四我们继续审理
We'll recess until Thursday.
女浩克的预约
- Appointment for She-Hulk.
-我们说你是个复仇者 -什么
- We told him you're an Avenger. - What?
标签上的各种注意事项都看仔细了
...all of the care instructions on the tag.
我可不为顾客的愚蠢行为买单
I will not be held responsible for customer stupidity.
这个
This one.
天啊
Oh, my God!
最近是有丑八怪大会吗
Is the hag convention in town?
卢克 我是妮基·拉莫斯 这位是女浩克
Luke, Nikki Ramos. This is the She-Hulk.
-珍妮佛·沃尔特斯 -没听说过
- Jennifer Walters. - Never heard of you.
我的客人都不一般 因为我的衣服无可挑剔
My client list is very exclusive because my work is impeccable.
我之前可告诉过你 她会成为复仇者联盟的一员
Well, like I told you before, she's gonna be one of the Avengers.
-你上次说她已经是了 -还没正式对外宣布
- You said she was one. - It hasn't been announced yet.
他们正在确认最后的细节 其实她已经是了
They're still working out the deal, but she is.
浩克可是她表哥
The Hulk is her cousin.
-有血缘关系吗  -当然
- By blood? - Yeah.
而且她会成为超级巨星
And she is going to be a megastar.
-她  -有必要搞得这么复杂吗
- Her? - Okay, is this really necessary?
我就是想要身新套装
I just want you to make me a new suit.
好吧 那你有什么超能力
Okay, what kind of superhero-ing do you do?
你需要内置武器的  还是可以防水防火的
Do you need built-in weaponry? Waterproofing, fire-resistance?
不 我不需要那种特殊服装 我只要一套商务套装
No, I don't need a suit like that. I just need a business suit.
我制作的衣服 都是符合最高战斗等级的
Everything I make stands up to the highest combat standards.
我可不做那些大路货
I don't make basic shit.
好吧 但是我确实用不上那种衣服 我是一名律师
Yeah, I don't really need any of that. I'm a lawyer.
她是个... 你是...
She's a... You're a...
-一名律师 -她是个律师
- A lawyer. - She's a lawyer.
真可爱 我喜欢 太可爱了
That's so cute. I love that. That's so cute.
这件 谢谢
This one. Thank you.
这简直就是在浪费我的时间和才华 请你们出去
This is a waste of my time and my talents. Please get out.
好吧 但是她需要的那种套装
Okay, but she needs a suit
得同时适合珍妮佛和女浩克
that's gonna fit her both as Jen and as She-Hulk.
这可非常需要才华 我们能给他展示一下吗
Something that requires a lot of talent. Can we show him?
对 得无缝切换 从小号 娇小玲珑
Yeah. All the way down, small, impish.
到大号 超能人类
- Large, superhuman.
你觉得你能做出 同时适合我两种身材的套装吗
Do you think you could design a suit that would adapt to both of my bodies?
怎么样 你之前没给浩克做过衣服吧
Come on. Ever done a Hulk before?
-这可是笔大生意啊 -廷斯利
- This is huge. This is huge. - Tinsley!
再给我订一卷弹性的羊毛 这单要用的面料
Order extra bolts of the stretch wool. We're going to need
可真不少
a lot of fabric.
-那人怎么阴阳怪气的  -时尚圈就是这个风格
Why was he so mean? In fashion, it's cool to be mean.
她简直是完美 她的衣服是在哪买的
She's so impeccable. Where does she shop?
肯定是什么高档地方
Somewhere with valet parking.
不会吧 还记得我那个约会对象吗 那个崇拜狂
Oh, no. Remember that date I went on with the guy with the fetish?
-我认识她 -当然
- I know her. - She's a client. Of course, you do.
他这个人又奇怪又恶心 不正常
He's so creepy and disgusting. Monstrous.
-嗨 托德 对吧  -女浩克
- Hi! Todd, right? - She-Hulk!
没想到你在这工作啊
Didn't know you worked here.
是啊 你是我们的客户 还是...
Yeah! Are you a client, or...
我是 还是大客户呢
I am. I'm one of the biggest.
刚见完我最喜欢的女律师
Just had a meeting with my favorite lady lawyer.
别碰我
No touching.
我们应该...
We should, um...
对 找个时间聚聚
Yeah, we should reconnect soon.
-好啊 太好了 -对 这次我请
- Absolutely. That would be great. - Yeah. Drinks on me.
好的
Okay.
-你答应得可真够快的 -太快了
- You rolled over so quickly. - So quickly.
-至少这次是他买单 -确实太快了
- But the drinks are on him. - So quickly.
十点外面见
See you outside in ten.
对 看看那个家伙的约会资料 你会说
Yeah, and you looked at that guy's dating profile and you were like,
“我就在他身上 浪费一两个小时的生命吧”
"I'll give him a couple of precious hours of my life."
然后我就坐在...不 是女浩克
And I sat across... No, She-Hulk.
女浩克就坐在他对面 吃完了整顿晚餐
She-Hulk sat across from him for an entire dinner.
他肯定会到处去和他的朋友说
Yeah, and he for sure is telling all his friends like,
“哥们 我和女浩克约会了”
"Yo, bro. Went on a date with She-Hulk."
-天啊 -怎么了
- Oh, my God. - What?
他是和女浩克约的会
He went on a date with She-Hulk.
对
Yeah.
因为我的约会资料是女浩克
Because I made a dating profile as She-Hulk,
然后以女浩克的身份去了好几次 这就说明我平时频繁使用这个名字
and went on several dates as She-Hulk, showing a clear pattern of using the name.
跟女浩克约会过的每个对象 都能为我作证
Every single one of those dates is a corroborating witness. This...
这样我就能赢下这个案子了
Is how I win this case.
但是你约的这些奇怪的男人 得挨个在法庭上出场
By parading all the questionable men you dated in a courtroom.
-珍妮佛 这可有点丢人 -是啊
- Jen, that's going to be embarrassing. - Yeah.
布克小姐
Ms. Book.
法官大人 我们有强有力的证据 可以证明我的委托人
Your Honor, we have compelling evidence my client did in fact self-identify
早在泰坦妮亚注册商标之前
with the moniker She-Hulk
就已经在以“女浩克” 这个名字自称了
well before Titania filed for the trademark.
请继续
Please proceed.
我的委托人 使用“女浩克”这个名字
My client used "She-Hulk,"
并非是要利用这个名字来销售商品
not as a name to exploit in order to sell product,
而是作为其身份真实的组成部分
but as a genuine part of her identity.
您可以在“自我介绍”这一栏看到 我的委托人是这样写的
As you can see in the "About Me" section, my client wrote, and I quote,
“身为绿皮恶女 我有翘臀长腿”
"Mean, green and straight-poured into these jeans."
在回答“你的理想伴侣是什么样的” 这个问题时
And to answer the question, "What are you looking for in a partner?"
我的委托人写到
my client wrote,
“一张坚固持久耐用的大床”
"A sturdy back and reinforced king-size bed.
“开玩笑的”
"JK. JK. JK."
现在有请证人出庭
We'd like to call our witnesses.
你好啊
'Sup?
对 她说 “是我 女浩克本人 有没有吓到你 ”
Yeah, she's like, "It's me. The real She-Hulk. Impressed much?"
说实话 她有点太刻意了
She came across a little tryhard, to be honest.
我对她说的没什么感觉
I'm just not about that.
我很清楚地记得她自称女浩克
I specifically remember her referring to herself as She-Hulk,
我从一个作家的角度客观地说
in the third person, and as a writer myself,
这个名字弱爆了
I found that grating.
对 不 她向我倾诉
Yeah, no, she confided in me
说她最开始觉得 “女浩克”这个名字有点丢人
that she was initially embarrassed by the name She-Hulk.
但是后来慢慢接受了
But then she embraced it.
我觉得这是最大的亮点
That's the beautiful part.
女人都愿意向我这样的人倾诉衷肠
I guess I'm the kind of guy a woman can really open up to.
你说你真正了解过“女浩克”
So you would say you really connected with She-Hulk?
女浩克和我有更加深入的接触
She-Hulk and I had an intense connection.
我们有过一次很棒的约会
We had a great date.
她还去打了些恶魔 挺酷的
She battled demons, I mean, come on.
假如你见到的不是女浩克
Would you have gone on the date
而是珍妮佛·沃尔特斯 你还会继续这个约会吗
if She-Hulk had instead presented as Jennifer Walters?
这个 我并不想失礼 但是...
Look, I don't mean to be rude, but...
不会
No.
她本人不是我喜欢的类型
She's not really my type.
但是女浩克就不一样了 女浩克很厉害 她太迷人了
But She-Hulk. She-Hulk's incredible. She's amazing.
根据最新的证人证词 法庭判定胜诉方为...
In light of this new testimony, the court finds in favor of...
珍妮佛·沃尔特斯 又名女浩克
Jennifer Walters, aka She-Hulk.
同时批准你方即决判决的动议
Motion for summary judgement is granted.
泰坦妮亚及其子公司
Titania and her subsidiaries will cease usage
必须立刻停止对 “女浩克”名称的使用
of the She-Hulk name effective immediately.
目前在市场上流通的所有产品 必须被召回
All current products on the market must be recalled.
这事我跟你没完 混蛋
This isn't over, hater.
-嘿 泰坦妮亚 -干什么
- Hey, Titania. - What?
我很抱歉你输了官司
I'm so sorry that happened to you.
-你等会有事吗  -好吧 你可以帮我买单 走吧
- What you getting into later? - Fine. You can buy me things. Let's go.
嘿
Hey.
我爱你 泰坦妮亚
I love you so much, Titania.
泰坦妮亚
MAN 2: Titania!
谢谢你
Thank you for that.
我得约几次心理咨询才能缓过来
I mean, I might need to schedule several sessions of therapy,
但是我们赢了
but we won.
听着 沃尔特斯
Look, Walters,
刚才那个帅哥说的
what that extremely attractive man said in there,
别信他的话 你会遇到更好的人
you can do better. You deserve better.
-我能请你喝一杯吗 聊表谢意 -当然
- Can I buy you a drink to say thanks? - Sure.
这杯是你的 真高兴能一起喝酒
Here you go. I'm so happy we're doing this.
干杯
Cheers.
全靠你破釜沉舟
Quite a strategy.
我还真没见过哪个律师
I don't know any other lawyer
为了赢案子连面子都不要了
who would humiliate themselves that way to win a case.
对啊 需要做出牺牲的时候 找我准没错
Yeah, you can always count on me to throw myself under the bus.
要不然霍利韦也不会付我 还算体面的薪水
It's why Holliway pays me the medium bucks.
他可没经历过你经历的这些
He couldn't have gone through that.
他从来不需要向一群平庸的男人 证明自己的价值
He's never had to prove his value to a parade of underwhelming men.
不是吗
Right?
女浩克有那么多能力
Like, think about everything that She-Hulk brings to the table,
这几个男人居然是我的最佳选择
and those guys were my best option.
你可是真的拥有超能力
You can have literal superpowers,
那些家伙会上个网 就觉得自己天下无敌了
and some guy with Internet will still think he can do better.
没错 天啊 这种事我们还得忍着
Yes! Oh, my God! The things we put up with.
真开心我们现在是朋友了
I am so happy we're friends now.
这...我刚才是不是说出来了
What... Did I just say that out loud?
-谢谢你请我喝酒 -应该的
- Thanks for the drink. - Of course.
我还以为今天你能穿得好看点呢
I thought you were getting better clothes.
对 我的衣服
Oh, yeah, my clothes!
嗨 卢克
Hey, Luke.
我是来取衣服的
Just here to get my suits.
给 去试试吧
Here. Try this.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我太喜欢了
Ooh! I like it!
那还用说 我可是天才
Of course you do, because I'm a genius.
我还给你准备了点别的
I made you a little something extra.
-我不太确定我真的能... -只要说谢谢就行了 珍妮佛
- I don't know that I'll really have an... - Just say thank you, Jennifer.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂 为什么不把这个收起来
Hello, this shouldn't be left out in the open.
廷斯利 客户保密协议 对你来说就是一团废纸吗
Tinsley, does client confidentiality mean nothing to you?
取货
根据漫威漫画改编
美丽与力量 女浩克签名版
女浩克翘臀霜 泰坦妮亚出品
漫威影业出品
《律师女浩克》
字幕翻译: 虫二